{
    "subject": "resource/Bruce_Willis",
    "predicate": "ontology/citizenship",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Bruce Willis is a citizen of the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9882521033287048,
            "question": "Is Bruce Willis a citizen of the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9851207733154297,
            "question": "Is Bruce Willis an American citizen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9526698589324951,
            "question": "Does Bruce Willis hold American citizenship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8493384718894958,
            "question": "Which country claims Bruce Willis as its citizen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8434813618659973,
            "question": "What is Bruce Willis' citizenship status?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5926656126976013,
            "question": "Where is Bruce Willis from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5001697540283203,
            "question": "What is Bruce Willis' nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4933483302593231,
            "question": "To which country does Bruce Willis belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48499757051467896,
            "question": "What is Bruce Willis' nationality status?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42904213070869446,
            "question": "In what country was Bruce Willis born?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bruce Willis is a citizen of the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7830_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Bruce Willis' nationality status?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7830_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Bruce Willis belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7830_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Bruce Willis' nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7830_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7830_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7830_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7830_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7830_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7830_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7830_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7830_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7830_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7830_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7830_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's my evaluation:\n\n* Birthdate and place of birth (Idar-Oberstein, West Germany) do not directly imply citizenship. However, it is mentioned that \"His family moved to the U.S. shortly after he was born\" and that his father was an American soldier.\n* Later on, in several documents, it's stated that Bruce Willis is described as an \"American actor\", \"an American actor and producer\", or simply \"American\".\n* Considering this information together, I conclude that the triple can be supported.\n\nTherefore:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents mention that Bruce Willis was born to an American father and moved to the U.S. shortly after his birth, indicating he has U.S. citizenship. Therefore, the statement \"Bruce Willis is a citizen of the United States\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}